Anquavious Grant

Software Engineer

+1 (470) 585-9591

agrant022@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/AnquaviousGrant

Atlanta, GA

EDUCATION

BA in Film and Video

HDI Support Center Analyst

Georgia State University, 2015

✓ KCS V5.3 Certification

MS in Project Management

Troy University, 2020

✓ Bomgar Certification A+

Full Stack Software Developer Certification

Georgia Institute of Technology

SKILLS

- Leadership
- Decision-making
- Critical Thinking
- Problem Solving
- Time Management
- Attention To Detail
- Documentation
- Creativity
- Adaptability

Profile

Forward-thinking IT professional with **+10** years of experience managing, supporting, and meeting the needs and the company's objectives.

I make sure that systems run smoothly behind the scenes so that a company can operate efficiently, all while managing teams and dealing with day-to-day concerns, planning, ensuring data security, and supervising website development. I am well-versed in a wide range of operating systems and have extensive knowledge of the complexities of IT platforms and software applications, as well as the ability to quickly learn new tools and technologies and provide strong support in IT Service Management, including ITIL certifications.

Strong team leader who excels at driving strategies across multiple work streams. Proficient at Developing

Experience

SR. IT AGENT 2015 -

- Effectively utilize ServiceNow tool to manage ticketing queue consistently to make sure all tickets are updated or resolved expeditiously.
- Adhere to all Standard Operating Procedures by confirming knowledge and gathering all pertinent details to drive towards most accurate resolution for restaurants.
- Contribute to the knowledge centered support by flagging articles for further review and creating articles for any new or unfamiliar issues that arise within Chick-fil-A restaurants.
- Demonstrates trustworthy decorum by always arriving promptly and utilize all available resources provided, such as remote access tools, weekly newsletters, and monitoring tools.
- Providing project reporting to executives including weekly status reports and retrospective meetings.
- Troubleshoot special IT products and conduct formal reviews with people leader after completion to confirm acceptance and technical satisfaction

JUNIOR PROJECT MANAGER

2014 - 2015

The Coca-Cola Company, ATLANTA

- Managed new product rollouts and launches under the Coca-Cola umbrella, incorporating SWOT and PESTLE analysis to determine weaknesses and assets.
- Implemented advanced knowledge of application, data, and infrastructure disciplines to create project plans, schedules, documentation, and quality management plans.
- Identified new business opportunities for Share a Coke, assisted with risk management and ensured that all project resources were allocated appropriately.
- Observed and reported project milestones and deadlines, as well as project status, and progress.
- Assist in the analysis, development, and recommendation of new projects for Coke.com testing and change requests.

METHODS

- IT Project Management
- SLA's Management
- Business Analysis
- IT Service Analyst
- Strategy Development
- Process Improvement
- System Implementation
- Staff Development
- IT Help Desk Specialist
- Technical Support
- Architecture Design
- Software Improvement
- Programming Languages

TECHNOLOGIES

- Windows and Linux
- Software / Hardware
- Java, JavaScript
- HTML5, CSS, QPID
- Oracle and Cassandra
- REST APIs and Ansible
- Async
- Relic Monitoring Software
- Jenkins and Docker
- Cloud Development

Experience Cont.

TECH SUPPORT SUPERVISOR

2012 - 2014

Telrite Company, COVINGTON

- Monitored team activities to ensure productivity and compliance with department standards to achieve organizational goals.
- Conducted quality control phone call monitoring to evaluate team performance and identify strengths and weaknesses.
- Ensure high-quality work is performed when developing large-scale, available services using various database and messaging technologies.
- Implemented weekly team meetings to keep staff members up to date on the latest information and to share knowledge of software-related competencies such as business analysis, development, and software improvement with the group.
- Supplied one-on-one coaching and advancement to each team member on a regular and timely

MOBILITY LEAD SPECIALIST

2012 - 2013

Career Connection. Inc./ Apple. Inc, ATLANTA

- Coordinated with other members of the Apple cross-functional team.
- Identified renewal risk and collaborated with internal teams ensuring successful regenerations.
- Resolved phone, e-mail, e-care, correspondence, TTY, and online chat inquiries.
- Processed and handled credit checks, service activations and changes, and receivables management/collection; with the ability to work independently, collaboratively, and effectively multitask when necessary.
- Maintained a working knowledge of all products, services, and promotions to provide recommendations based on the needs of the customer.
- Successfully resolve escalation by identifying, tracking, and trending issues to aid in root cause